NAVAS CIFUENTES JONATHAN G.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Fullstack web developer, focused on providing professional technical solutions complying with software quality standards as well as the use of current technologies.

I'm very interested in topics related to clean architectures, TDD, mobile application programming, i'm constantly updating my knowledge with online courses.

I have experience working as a freelance developer which has allowed me to code from web pages to robust enterprise systems.

Experience

Fullstack Developer - Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Design and development of a corporate website for a gastronomic coach "Ricardo Rivadeneira" in Ecuador using technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php and Php-Mailer

Design and development of a professional website for the advertising agency "Pc Creativa". I used technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php and PhpMailer

Freelance Developer - Feb 2020 - Present

Design and development of a web platform (SADGEC) for the monitoring and control of compliance with recommendations of the Comptroller General of the State. Which includes modules of report management, control of personnel and positions of public officials for government entities for the company "Planet-It".

Redesign and development of a platform for the sale of practical theoretical courses of martial arts for the company Zen-Sei. I used technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php, PhpMailer. I also implemented the Paypal payment gateway for the purchase of course coupons.

Design and development of a web platform (SACVI) for the management of vacation licenses in governmental entities for the company "Planet-It". I used technologies such as Ht-ml,Css (Bootstrap 4.5) - AdminLte, PhpMailer, Mysql database.



Contact

+593 982329901

ionathan.navas9@hotmail.com

nttps://github.com/jonathannavas

nttps://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-gabriel-navas/

Education

Universidad de las Fuerzas Armadas ESPE

Software Engineer Oct 2014 - Sept 2021

Certiprof

Scrum Master Professional Apr 2021

Howard Institute

English language proficiency Sept 2011

Skills

Front-end

Html

Css - (Uikit, Materialize, Bootstrap)

Javascript - React (Learning)

Back-end

Java / Springboot

Php

Javascript / Node is / Express JS (API REST, JWT)

Databases

MySql

MongoDB

Cloud Services

Heroku

Mongo Atlas

Control Version

Git

Github